[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "It kind of took the wind out of your sails, didn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "It did, but, you know, it's about to land bashing (ph) for running a terrible system.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Some of the last two weeks, I mean has it been as I said a comedian's dream this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "POS", "NN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "They said that about everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Well, I think the country in general is on a decline.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "I mean she's somebody carry the can for the fact the system has started so badly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "DT", "MD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "You know, I'm not a big fan of scapegoating.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Ever?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Well, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Why get rid of her now to make it -- make the situation worst?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "But when she says we're going to be bring in the A-Team.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Hang on a second, she's the president's great initiative?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Oh, I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "... before?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "That's actually true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Is he really credible that the President whose massive legacy maybe based around this, didn't know anything about anything problematic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "WP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Not credible and not excusable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Just to clarify you don't like cat videos, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "I've actually never seen one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Genuine whistleblower?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "No concerns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "What is the line?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "What we really don't want is a rogue agency.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Why is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Well, because I think for one, we don't care to learn about other countries.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "I read -- now this week it was two stories in the news and had to do with race, the Julianne, how -- is that how you pronounce that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WRB", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Yeah, (inaudible) the face off you.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Julianne"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ":", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "What you make in her argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "It's always perfect -- perfectly wrong, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Could it be him against Chris Christie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "It probably will be.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "You mean oversees, what are they saying about him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "What would it mean for America and for America's reputations, you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "You know, we don't know until he -- if he became president.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Will it ever change?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Probably not in my lifetime.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Less people have more guns, isn't that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RBR", "NNS", "VBP", "JJR", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "And will just a federal law encompassing the whole of America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Absolutely, I mean that's what happens when the tipping point is reached with the states, I think that's what would happen with gay marriage and probably some day with marijuana itself.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "You're asking me to choose between my children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Carlin"]}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Will you literally do stand up until the day they carry you out in a box?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "George Carlin did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Will that be your dream exit from life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "It would be a great way to go.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2029"]}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Truthfully you want to live to be 100?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Well, I'm hoping Reichert Well (ph) is correct and I'll live forever because, you know, he says that what he calls the singularity that's coming in the year 2029 points out that we're already partly machine, people have all kinds of stents and artificial hearts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", ",", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Does it matter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "AHER: Well, it does matter because when we didn't use to have this kind of places where you could retreat to your, you know, (inaudible) of thinking, public discourse was the better for it because you had to hear a conflicting idea, now you don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "NN", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "Wrestling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "That doesn't get him staying, nothing will.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jay Leno"]}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "What do you make of Jay Leno?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "I like Jay Leno.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jay Leno"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "Is it jealousy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "Oh, well, of course a lot of it is that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jay"]}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "He does himself right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "He doesn't have someone talking in the ear of the network executive like the other guys do saying, get rid of Jay, he's too old.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "Do you have an agent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "... so he would listen -- of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]